

# Luka Tsiklauri

Software Developer

Tbilisi, Georgia +995 574-830-661 info.tsiklauri@gmail.com

### **ABOUT ME**

A software developer with over 6 years of experience, motivated to lead and take a full responsibility in developing your software product. always honest, always transparent. The 3 key that leads me to create successful software are:

- 1. Discipline
- 2. Passion for success
- 3. The result

#### **SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES**

- Strong analytical & problem solving skills
- Lean, Agile, Scrum and Kanban frameworks
- · Strategic thinking and planning skills

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certificate in <u>Cyber security</u>
 Business & Technology University
 2021

Certificate in <u>Business & Finances</u>
Georgian National University
2020

Certificate in <u>Web Development</u>
 Intellect center
 2017

### **WORK HISTORY**

### SIDES GmbH - Back-End Developer

Mar 2022 - Feb 2023

Senior PHP developer - I've been managing development team, collaborating with stakeholders and developing POS and payment systems.

## TBC net (MY.GE LTD) - Back-End Developer

Feb 2021 - Jan 2022

I was developing the largest web-platform in Georgia <a href="mymarket.ge">mymarket.ge</a> by implementing a complex software system and optmizing website for millions of users

- PHP OOP, Lumen, SQL, GraphQL, CI/CD
- Javascript, ReactJs
- Flutter & Dart

### Freelancer Full-Stack Developer

Jan 2017 - NOW

I actively participate in the process of analyzing customer needs and provide back-end/front-end solutions using the following technologies:

- PHP, Laravel, SQL, NoSQL, SaaS
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, ReactJs
- Dart & Flutter

### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

### **Georgian Technical University**

ΙT

2020 - 2022

# Moscow Institute of Physic & Technology

Algorithms & Data structures (online courses) **2020** 

## **Intellect Center**

Web development courses

2016-2017

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

## Front-End

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript jQuery, ReactJs

## Back-End

- PHP, Laravel **5.1 10.x**
- MySQL, SQL, NoSQL
- GraphQL
- WordPress

# Cross-platform

- Flutter & Dart
- Firebase

### General

- Algorithms & Data Structures
- Big O
- OOP SOLID principles + 24 Design patterns
- Clean Architecture & Clean code by Robert Martin

### Other

- KISS, SOLID, DRY
- Concurrent, Reactive, Functional
- REST/SOAP API, TCP/IP Sockets
- MVC, MVVM, Lifting State
- TDD, BDD
- GIT, Jira, Codemagic, CI/CD, Zoho
- A/B testing + User Behaviour analytic + Crash logging

## **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

- Georgian Native
- English C1
- Russian C1
- German A2-B1